undergroundreptiles.com 2007-12-02

# Underground Reptiles - Store Policies

|  | 

[ ](https://secure2.activeserverhosting.com/undergroundreptiles-com/ugstore/advcart.asp) February 19, 2020  
  
---  

|    
---  
  
SHIPPING • PRIVACY • RETURN

Underground Reptiles has been shipping reptiles for almost 20 years. We have been on the cutting edge of safety for the animal, yet maintaining the cost effectiveness for you, the customer. We strive daily to find new ways to ship your animals with an accent on comfort and care for the reptiles that we ship. We adhere strictly to IATA regulations and guidelines put forth by the government and airlines.  

We ship via UPS to your door, or via airfreight on commercial airlines. Our dry goods are shipped via USPS Priority Mail or UPS ground, whichever costs less. For those of you with accounts, we will be happy to ship on your account, using our fine packaging.  

We use only the finest packaging materials and package enhancers, including, but not limited to, Styrofoam boxes, 40-hour heat packs, and ice packs designed to stay colder longer (for shipping amphibians).   

With Underground Reptiles, we give you one less thing to worry about. You will receive your animal alive, in top shape, and ready to be your pet.  

**TERMS**

We guarantee live arrival on all animals, **except** amphibians and arachnids. We guarantee all animals to be healthy and eating at time of purchase. We CANNOT, however, be responsible for the way in which you choose to keep your animals. We will be more than happy to send you a care sheet with our recommendations of care or check out our Care Sheets section for our most popular animals.

**SHIPPING FEES**

UPS Next Day Air service (for all animals) is $40 & up (for larger animals). We have found this service to be the most reliable for the price. We will gladly provide your tracking number at the time of your order, or we can email it to you at the earliest convenience.

Our dry goods shipping costs are estimated shipping. We try our best to estimate the correct amount. You will be charged for exact shipping - _we do not charge handling: we don't believe that you should profit on shipping_! If the difference between estimated and exact shipping is greater than $5, we will contact you.

****

We are very flexible. We are here to serve you and we get no joy from a bad situation or deal that is not mutually beneficial. We also will never get a repeat customer unless you are completely satisfied. The unfortunate side of any industry is that there are many factors involved in making a deal prosperous for all concerned parties. And from time to time, the occasional (unusual) negative experience can happen. We try to keep this to an extreme minimum and will do all in our power both socially and financially to make your experience with our company a positive one. WHAT'S OUR POINT? Be kind, be nice, and we will be, too. We will work with you in every way to satisfy your concerns. 

**Underground Reptiles Return Policy**

Underground Reptiles is committed to providing quality animals and dry goods to our customers. We guarantee that animals are healthy and eating at time of purchase, unless otherwise stated. We offer a live-arrival guarantee with the following exceptions:

No live arrival guarantee to places where UPS cannot deliver by 10:30 a.m.

No live arrival guarantee on any amphibians

No live arrival guarantee on animals that are misplaced or lost by UPS, including but not limited to incorrect address information.

Deceased animals will be replaced with another animal of the same species. Underground Reptiles reserves the right to issue a store credit or offer an alternative animal in the event that the same species is not available. **All animals listed are "ALL SALES FINAL".** We cannot be responsible if you changed your mind about what type of animal you want! However, if we do allow a return according to our discretion, any animals returned will be charged a 20% restocking fee. This restocking fee also applies to cancelled orders. Shipping fees are non-refundable.

Underground Reptiles will not purposely misrepresent any animal that is for sale. If for any reason you are not satisfied with your purchase, simply notify us by e-mail within 24 hours of receiving your animal. We will work with you to rectify the situation. In these situations, we generally require you to return the animal. **We will not ever refund money if the animal is still in your possession.** If we determine a refund is due, actual shipping charges paid by Underground Reptiles will be deducted from the purchase price, unless the return is due to our error. 

Underground Reptiles will not be liable for care provided in a matter that is inconsistent with our care sheets. We cannot be responsible for gross neglect or improper care. We do offer a wide variety of books that can be purchased to further enhance the purchaser's knowledge of the species. We will be happy to furnish a care sheet and diet sheet (if applicable) to you upon request.

If dry goods are received damaged, please provide a picture of the damage and a new replacement item will be shipped. If you are not pleased with your dry goods purchase, you may return it (shipping cost is customer's responsibility) for store credit only. All dry goods listed are "ALL SALES FINAL". Shipping costs are non-refundable.

Underground Reptiles makes every effort to represent our dry goods accurately. Please feel free to email us any questions regarding products before making your purchase.  

****

**Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**

> **a..Our Commitment To Privacy   
>  b.. The Information We Collect   
>  c.. Our Commitment To Data Security   
>  d.. Our Commitment To Children's Privacy   
>  e.. How To Access Or Correct Your Information   
>  f.. How To Contact Us**

* * *

**Our Commitment To Privacy**   
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and on every webpage that we have on the internet. 

**The Information We Collect:**   
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Underground Reptiles website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

> a.. Name   
>  b.. Address   
>  c.. Email address   
>  d.. Phone number   
>  e.. Credit/Debit Card Information 

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.   

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**   
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.   

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**   
You cannot access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online at this time.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.   

**How To Contact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (954) 428.8434 or send us an email at [info@undergroundreptiles.com](mailto:info@undergroundreptiles.com%20).

|
